Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
EMERGENCY MEDICAL SERVICES
Are you all right?
-Did you see that woman's body?
-Yes. It's unfortunate.
She was just standing there.
EPISODE 2
THE REASON YOU'RE GOING TO HELL
I'm going to make it!
How could he think of jumping
without a parachute?
He's so reckless.
And you jumped off the roof.
How are you any better?
Shall we move on to your next death?
Wait.
-Let's talk.
-About what?
You said I could survive.
but I died the moment I opened my eyes.
All these deaths are inevitable.
They're avoidable.
How?
That's for you to figure out.
What?
I died even after
I was given his abilities!
My head burst.
and my damned neck snapped!
I said this was a punishment.
It's natural that it's painful.
I'm sorry.
About what?
About referring to death as just a means.
It's too late.
Your sin is great enough
to even anger God.
What? What did I do?
-The fact that I killed myself?
-It's much bigger than that.
You'll need to find out what that sin is.
If you fail to figure it out.
you'll go to hell.
even after you've survived this.
But why did you kill yourself?
Because
all I could see was darkness...
whether my eyes were open or shut.
I was born into a poor family
and struggled to improve my life.
but I still failed to get a job.
I even lost all the money I had...
and had to let go of the woman I loved.
There wasn't any hope left in my life.
So you killed yourself
because your life felt hopeless?
Is that so wrong?
It's not like I did harm to anyone.
Think carefully
if you really didn't harm anyone.
I won't bother.
It's over for me already. so why should I?
So that you can regret it
and repent.
Will I go to heaven if I regret it now?
Will repenting
give me another chance at life?
I won't do it.
You really must not care
about anything but yourself.
What else should I care for
other than myself?
Then find a way to survive on your own.
And stop whining about it to me.
What? This is a school.
Am I a teacher?
Or...
I need to find a mirror.
Damn it.
Is he a high schooler?
Or maybe he's in middle school.
But how does he end up dying?
This punk always cracks me up.
That bastard...
He's laughing while watching
a video of someone dying.
How can someone be so stupid?
My name is Kwon Hyeok-su.
I'm 17 years old.
After my dad passed away when I was five.
-my mom became the family's breadwinner.
-Why are you still up?
She worked tirelessly
day and night to support me.
Seeing her work so hard
made me think I should study harder.
but I hate going to school.
Here's some milk to help you grow.
You need it to grow tall.
You should have brought me my money.
Hey.
-Take a photo.
-Okay.
Look over this way.
Look into the camera.
Look over here. you idiot.
Why don't you smile a little?
You should smile.
I love you. son. I'll see you later.
But I couldn't help but go to school.
If she were to find out
I was being bullied...
Go on.
...my existence would become
nothing but guilt that weighed her down.
I became confused
as my hellish school life continued.
Did school become hell
because my bullies are demons.
or did I end up falling into hell
because of something I had done?
Feeling that I couldn't
carry on living like this.
I made a big decision.
If you bully me again.
I'm going to jump off the roof.
I mean it.
You idiot.
You think anyone will care if you die?
Lower your hand.
I said. lower it.
You pathetic moron.
If you plan on dying.
you better bring me my milk first.
Or I'll beat you to death myself.
With that. I decided to end my life
and was on my way up to the roof.
What a moron.
It must be him.
HE POURED HIS STRAWBERRY MILK
OVER MY HEAD AGAIN...
So Hyeok-su must have
killed himself like me.
Damn it.
I can't believe I'm a high schooler
who's being bullied.
Wait.
Then that means I won't die
unless I kill myself.
I feel sorry for Hyeok-su.
but I just managed to avoid death.
I don't have to go to hell.
What are you laughing about. idiot?
Didn't I tell you to get me
a strawberry milk?
If I get back from smoking
and the milk isn't on my desk.
you're dead meat.
Moron.
His head must be made of stone.
Hey!
What are you looking at?
You must be itching to die. insolent punk!
-You son of a bitch.
-Have you lost it?
You pathetic loser.
You motherfucker.
-He's strong.
-You're dead. you useless punk.
If anyone tries to stop me. you're dead.
Bet you think you're hot shit.
But there are things
way worse than you in this world.
Don't mess with me from now on.
Got that?
Apologize.
Apologize!
Why should I. you prick?
What do you think you're doing?
What's it to you?
Just die!
Motherfucker.
What the hell's gotten into you?
You hit me while my guard was down.
you son of a bitch.
And with a fucking chair.
You fucking coward!
Am I wrong?
Am I wrong or not?
You're right.
Yes. that's right.
-That was a cheap shot.
-You assholes!
I'm the coward?
Me?
Then how is this any different?
You must have a death wish.
The teacher's coming!
Once school's out.
you're dead.
Even in the wide and open countryside.
he began to make time for himself.
-Now. what does it say...
-Damn it.
It wouldn't matter if it was just him.
I can't do anything
if that big guy comes at me too.
No matter how young they are.
I can't overcome the size difference.
What should I do?
Then find a way to survive on your own.
And stop whining about it to me.
I have to find a way.
YEONGWON HIGH SCHOOL
Jin-sang.
Let's stop now.
I think he got the message.
Let go of me!
Are you looking down on me too?
That's not it.
Come here.
Come on.
Let's get it together. Tae-seok.
All right?
I'm sorry.
Now go and hold him down.
Hold him down!
Hey. Jin-sang.
What are you doing?
Hey. Min-ji. Hi.
Hold on.
I need to teach this punk a lesson.
Stop it.
Fine. I'll go.
Watch your step. I'll see you out front.
I survived thanks to that girl.
Could she have done that to save me?
What are you looking at. moron?
Right.
There's no such thing
as a kind-hearted bully.
It feels so weird
to enter someone else's house
like it's mine.
It's so average.
I guess I'm not rich this time around.
Hyeok-su was raised
by a single mother like me.
HYEOK-SU. I'LL BE HOME LATE TODAY.
DON'T SKIP DINNER. I LOVE YOU.
Yee-jae. there's stew in the fridge.
so heat it up for dinner.
I love you. son.
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
Let me help.
There's no need for that.
Did you eat?
I'll eat with you
after I finish this quickly.
What?
Just go inside and have dinner. Go on.
I was raised
by a single mother in poverty.
It was never my goal
to become rich.
My humble wish was
to get a job. get married.
and start a family like everyone else.
But to me.
such common things
were an unattainable goal.
I made bulgogi. your favorite.
Why do you look so down?
Did something happen?
Not at all.
You're being so polite all of a sudden.
Is something up?
Nothing's up. Let's eat.
M...
Mom.
Sure. Dig in.
Yee-jae.
Eat as much as you like.
Mom...
It's fine.
Everything is fine. Yee-jae.
Hyeok-su.
You zoned out for a minute.
It's nothing.
Mom...
LEE JIN-SANG
You better bring me
50.000 won tomorrow. moron.
This bastard...
Pull yourself together.
It's my current life
that I need to focus on.
What's worse
than having to bring them money
is having to lie to Mom for that money.
It makes me hate myself
and makes me want to die.
Jin-sang. that bastard.
I have a feeling that I'm not the only one
who has a bone to pick with him.
Hyeok-su.
I'll make sure to pay that bastard back
for having driven you to your death.
It depicted
the turmoil that swept the era.
He was so immersed
-that he read them four times.
-First. I need to make him an ally.
-The reverence...
-Sir.
-May I use the restroom?
-Sure thing.
Taebaek Mountains taught him
the beauty of the Jeolla dialect.
Reading the series four times...
Tae-seok.
Can you beat Jin-sang in a fight?
What the hell are you on about?
Have you lost it?
What I'm saying is I was beaten
by both you and Jin-sang recently.
And I noticed that you were
much stronger than Jin-sang.
Are you some expert
at getting beaten up now?
What a lunatic.
Why you...
Should I try taunting him a little?
I don't get why he's the boss around here.
I don't get why you're scared of him
and let him slap you around like that.
What?
Have you really gone nuts?
Who says I'm scared of him?
He's still a teenager after all.
My point is.
why aren't you the boss
when you're much stronger?
Are you that curious
about why I let him slap me around?
Why he bosses me around?
Yes.
I'm just as annoyed
being bossed around by someone
even a loser like you can beat up.
But that's because...
What are you two doing in here?
I asked you a question.
I was just
putting him in his place.
He was getting out of line.
Is that so?
Well done.
-And Tae-seok.
-Yeah?
It hurts where I hit you. doesn't it?
Yes.
You should've known better.
Got it?
And you'll get the beating
you missed out on yesterday.
I think I have indigestion.
Hey.
You asked me
if I could beat him in a fight. right?
I could beat him with just one hand.
But I can't ever fight him one-on-one.
Do you know why?
Because his friend will come running
the moment I touch him.
A really strong one at that.
It's Seong-hyeop. a senior.
He's the strongest in this whole area.
All Jin-sang did
was take taekwondo with him
in elementary school.
Those sons of bitches...
You punks.
And now he's the boss here
for being in Seong-hyeop's clique
when he's just a wimp.
Cliques are the problem.
whether it's in school
or out in the world.
I need to come up with a plan.
Something that would work
on a high school kid.
The cafeteria food these days is amazing.
Are you enjoying the food?
You must be. seeing as
you dunked your whole face in it.
You're so gross.
Finish your food. moron.
Hey!
"Hey"?
Are you enjoying the food?
You must be. seeing as
you're practically showering in it.
Finish your food. then.
I'm off.
Damn it.
Fuck!
Tae-seok.
Go and grab that bastard.
Go fucking grab him!
I just got here.
I'll miss lunch if I chase after him now.
You should sit and eat too.
-What?
-Sit down.
Okay.
Have you lost your mind?
You might want to wash up.
And get changed too.
Damn it.
Are you sure
you'll be all right. Tae-seok?
I'm a little confused right now.
-Same here.
-What?
You want to get rid of Jin-sang.
don't you?
No matter what I do to Jin-sang.
don't get involved.
Then that senior won't ever mess with you.
He really did that?
Yes.
Can you please teach him a lesson?
I'm begging you. Seong-hyeop.
Sure.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
-Reading a webtoon.
-Are you insane?
Did you do all that without a plan?
-If anything happens to me...
-I do have a plan.
This is my plan.
What?
Hey.
Hey!
Did you pour noodles on Jin-sang?
No. I didn't.
It really wasn't me.
It wasn't?
No. It wasn't me.
Then who was it?
There.
It was him.
Hey. you.
Yes?
What is it?
What the hell?
He's a total nobody.
You're right. Damn it.
Unbelievable.
Did we come all the way here
to beat up a wimp like him?
This is embarrassing.
Jin-sang.
Jin-sang!
Yes?
You...
Did you ask for my help
because of this wimp?
Well. it's just...
He suddenly rushed at me.
Exactly!
Can't you handle
a wimp like him on your own?
Wait. but...
Never mind.
Let's go.
Where are you going. Seong-hyeop?
Don't go around
acting like we're close ever again.
Hold on.
Wait.
Looking cool is the only thing
that matters to guys like that.
They can't help but throw away
whatever cramps their style.
Hey.
You can talk to me now
if you've got something to say.
Your friend is gone now.
Wait a minute.
He's not your friend anymore.
You bastard.
Let go of me!
Damn it.
Does it hurt where I hit you?
You should've known better.
I told you. didn't I?
I can beat him with just one hand.
I've definitely made it now.
Jin-sang. who used to be the boss here.
was dethroned in the blink of an eye.
And since that day.
nobody ever dared to bully me again.
Damn it.
What was that?
What a moron.
He's a loner now that we've ditched him.
He's been such a prick.
No wonder he has no friends left.
Look. he's acting like he can't hear us.
I know he can hear me.
What are you looking at. moron?
I'll get myself into shape
and build some muscles too.
But when will I ever find a job
and save up money?
I'm worrying about money again.
It's all your fault.
Have you been drinking?
Sure.
It's all my fault
that you've ended up that way.
But do you know why I did that?
It was all because of you.
Do you get it?
Do you?
I doubt you do.
Moron.
What a moron.
What are you looking at. moron?
I can't believe how persistent he is.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Die.
Die!
It's all your fault!
What happened?
Damn it.
Don't tell me
that lunatic actually killed me.
All because his life got a little hard
when he bullied someone
to the point of death?
Isn't that what you humans do?
You care more about
the thorn in your own finger
than the knife inside someone else's body.
He was the one
who went around stabbing people!
How could he murder me over that
when he did far worse to others?
I should've given him
a stronger punishment.
I can't stand hearing that
from someone who's being punished.
Wait!
Was Hyeok-su really going to kill himself?
Did you pull some strings
since I figured that out
and managed to avoid death?
I'm right. aren't I?
I'm already destined to go to hell.
so why would you tell me
about all those rules?
You lied to me and gave me false hope.
I struggled so hard.
but it was all for nothing!
I never lie.
It may be fun to watch you struggle.
but I do not intervene
in the game you play.
There is no need for me
to resort to such things.
If you forget your manners again.
I will crush your face.
And if you ever kill yourself
while you're being punished.
you will come to face a pain
worse than hell itself.
Got that?
Yes.
Don't!
Just as you guessed.
Kwon Hyeok-su
was supposed to kill himself.
But the reason you died this way
had nothing to do with me
and was solely
due to the choices you made.
It can't be true.
Why not?
I died even after trying so hard.
I failed again.
I just don't know
what it is that I can do anymore.
It's no fun for me
if you end up giving up so easily.
Then
why don't you put me in a body
that isn't so difficult to survive in?
That would be even less fun.
What?
Just wait.
The pain that death brings you
will only get worse from now on.
What?
What's going on?
Why can't I see anything?
What is that noise?
Why can't I move?
Damn it. What's going on right now?
Hold him.
Talk.
What?
About what?
Where's the girl and the money?
Just pluck it out.
Hold still.
I'll do a clean job
since we used to be friends.
It's going to be messy if you struggle.
I'll talk!
I'll tell you! I swear!
But...
can you give me a moment?
What for?
I don't remember everything just yet.
-I'll tell you once I remember.
-Do you think this is a joke?
Enough.
Let me help you
refresh your memory.
My name is Lee Ju-hun.
I'm 35 years old.
I'm what you call a fixer.
The gang I'm a part of
has clients all across the globe.
It's quite a big secret organization
in the criminal world.
We fix our clients' problems
by any means necessary.
And that. of course...
-What the hell?
-Get him!
Who are you?
...includes murder.
I no longer want to live in this hell.
Let's leave together.
I stole ten billion
from my boss's secret slush fund
and stored it in a safe place.
However. as I was on my way
to meet up with her.
my boss ended up catching up to me.
You punk!
Come here!
That punk.
You bastard.
Take this!
-I'll teach you...
-Son of a bitch!
-Damn it!
-What the hell?
-Damn you!
-Show yourself!
Come here. you punk!
This guy sure leads a dramatic life.
But he could end up dead any moment.
Wait.
Why should I go on living as this man?
And if you ever kill yourself
while you're being punished.
you will come to face a pain
worse than hell itself.
Hold on.
He has ten billion...
That's right.
I'll end up dead no matter what I do.
And if I end up surviving.
I'll end up poor and miserable.
Let's find the ten billion he's hidden
so that I can retrieve it.
even if I end up as someone else.
That's how I'll escape
this game rigged by Death.
With this man's abilities.
I might have
a pretty good chance.
It's ten billion.
I'll put my life on the line.
Hot damn.
He's really good at riding motorcycles.
We lost Lee Ju-hun.
What?
CONNECTING
We'll now begin hunting down
the dog that bit his master.
I've uploaded Lee Ju-hun's coordinates.
Two billion?
Where are you going? Hey!
Lee Ju-hun.
I'll make sure you're dead
before the night is over.
NO TWO-WHEELED VEHICLES PAST THIS POINT
I'll catch you myself.
Are you still standing there?
Are you afraid to turn back?
The face I somberly remembered
The person I'm grateful for
The person I owe
Although there's no miracle we hoped for
Nor the strength to get back on our feet
Listen to the voice that embraces you
"I love you"
If you're still hesitating
I hope you find the courage
To stand up again
And overcome it
Subtitle: Sonya Hong
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm